<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore</string>
    <string name="sign_in">SIGN-IN</string>
    <string name="title">tile</string>
    <string name="description">The app would allow .</string>


    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign-Out</string>


    <string name="explore_intro">
        The app would allow different users to explore more about different communities now in British Columbia.
        The app would focus mainly on four communities ie.. India, Japan, Greek and Brazil.
        There would be two main categories that would be further categorized on the basis of communities.
        There would be a feature of Culture and Food through which the user would be able to traverse the communities stated above.
        There would be information about the events that would be in progress and allow the user to gather information about it.
    </string>

    <string name="culture_intro">
     This feature enables the user to explore more about the four different Countries being included in
the application - Brazil, India. The app is based on this feature which would allow users to attend
events from these regions and learn about them. This would also tell the users about the best
cuisines from these places in British Columbia.
    </string>

    <string name="tour_intro">
     This would allow the user to go on ventures and be a part of tranquility. The user will be able to
     see the top most rated adventures and relaxation places around them. This feature will allow the
     user to check how far there destination is from their location and they can plan their trip
     accordingly.
    </string>

    <string name="india_intro">
         The culture of India refers collectively to the thousands of distinct and unique
        cultures of all religions and communities present in India.
        India\'s languages, religions, dance, music, architecture, food,
        and customs differ from place to place within the country.
        Indian culture, often labeled as an amalgamation of several cultures,
        spans across the Indian subcontinent and has been influenced by a history that is several millennia old.
    </string>
 <string name="brazil_intro">The culture of Brazil is primarily Western, but presents a very diverse nature showing that an ethnic and cultural mixing occurred in the colonial period involving mostly Indigenous peoples of the coastal and most accessible riverine areas, Portuguese people and African people.</string>

    <string name="culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="tour">Tour</string>
    <string name="culture_title">Culture</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="categories_title">Categories</string>
    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="input_error_name">name required</string>
    <string name="input_error_email">email required</string>
    <string name="input_error_password">password required</string>

    <string name="input_error_password_length">password should be at least 6 characters long</string>
    <string name="registration_success">Registered Successfully</string>
    <string name="input_error_email_invalid">enter a valid email</string>
    <string name="event_pic">event pic</string>
    <string name="contact_android_string_emptyphonenumber">contact @android:string/emptyPhoneNumber</string>
    <string name="title_activity_location_page">Map</string>
    <string name="register_for">Register for</string>


    <string-array name="countries">
        <item>Select Country</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="categories">
        <item>Select category</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Event</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
